John Howard Society of the Lower Mainland of British Columbia fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- General administrative and office files, 1934 - 1990; F-1-3; 3.08 m of textual records
  - Administration, 1930 - 1990; F-1-3-1; 91 cm of textual records 45 photographs
    - Unarchived, 1930-1969; F-1-3-1-1; 2 cm of textual records
      - 1930-1940s Constitution, F-1-3-1-1-2 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
      - History 1931-1941, 1990; F-1-3-1-1-3 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Annual reports & financial statements, 1989 - 1992; F-1-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - J.O. Hobden scholarship fund, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - J.O. Hobden scholarship fund, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - J.O. Hobden scholarship fund, 1990; F-1-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Board of directors minutes, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Board of directors minutes, 1987 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Board of directors minutes, 1986 - 1987; F-1-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Board of directors minutes, vol. 1, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - Board of directors minutes, vol. 2, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - Staff meetings, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - 50th anniversary annual meeting photographs, vol. 1, 1981; F-1-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - 50th anniversary annual meeting photographs, vol. 2, 1981; F-1-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - Volunteer training, [ca 1980] - 1980; F-1-3-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 1-95)
    - Board of director list, 1982 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Board of director correspondence, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Board of direcgtor reference material, 1986 - 1992; F-1-3-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Board of director needs analysis survey, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Board of director - building - correspondence with SHC investments, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Newsletter, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Newsletter, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Correspondence - government; related organizations, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Correspondence - Interoffice memos, 1985 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Correspondence - Non-project agencies, 1982 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Correspondence - Private agencies, 1986 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Correspondence - Solicitor general, 1982 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Office - organizational charts, [ca 1980] - 1980; F-1-3-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Office - policy - media guide, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Office - policy - personnel policy, 1986; F-1-3-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Office - programs - reality therapy training, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - History - J.D. Hobden, [ca 1985] - 1985; F-1-3-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - History - organization & general information, 1987; F-1-3-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - History - reference material, 1988 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - History - society in Canada, [ca 1980] - 1980; F-1-3-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Staff - executive director - responsibilities, 1983 - 1994; F-1-3-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Staff - staff lists, 1985 - 1987; F-1-3-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Society - historical highlights, 1980 - 1995; F-1-3-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Society - mission statements, goals, 1980 - 1983; F-1-3-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Union - agreement, 1987 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Union - agreement, 1986 - 1987; F-1-3-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Union - agreement, 1985 - 1986; F-1-3-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Union - agreement, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 1-96)
    - Union - correspondence, 1985 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Union - grievances, 1985; F-1-3-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Union - grievances, 1984 - 1985; F-1-3-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Union - job postings, 1988 - 1992; F-1-3-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Union - negotiations - summary, 1986 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Union - salary survey, 1986 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHSBC Board of directors meetings agenda and minutes, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHSBC - correspondence, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHSBC - goals, mission statements, objectives, 1983 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHSBC - report to board, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS in BC - Kelowna, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-70 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS in BC - Vancouver Island, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-71 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS - other provinces - Alberta, 1979 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-72 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS - other provinces - Newfoundland, 1973; F-1-3-1-0-73 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS - national - JHS of Canada - correspondence, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-1-0-74 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - JHS - other provinces - Ottawa, 1988; F-1-3-1-0-75 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - MSSH - family services contract, 1986 - 1990; F-1-3-1-0-76 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - United way - Fraser Valley, 1987 - 1991; F-1-3-1-0-77 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - United way - Lower Mainland correspondence, 1987 - 1992; F-1-3-1-0-78 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Audited financial statements, 1990 - 1991; F-1-3-1-0-79 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - Property insurance, 1987 - 1995; F-1-3-1-0-80 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - Property management, 1982 - 1992; F-1-3-1-0-81 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Original constitution & bylaws, 1983 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-82 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - JHS of BC Minutes, reports, memos, 1988 - 1990; F-1-3-1-0-83 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - JHS of BC Minutes, reports, memos, 1991; F-1-3-1-0-84 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Annual General Meeting, 1987 - 1988; F-1-3-1-0-85 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Annual General Meeting, 1989; F-1-3-1-0-86 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Annual General Meeting, 1990; F-1-3-1-0-87 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Ministry of social services and housing contracts, 1991; F-1-3-1-0-88 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Victims of crime, 1991; F-1-3-1-0-89 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Conference: managing the criminal justice system: the victim, 1982; F-1-3-1-0-90 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Presentation to executive committee, ministry of attorney general on Project Restore, 1982; F-1-3-1-0-91 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
  - Projects, 1970 - 1995; F-1-3-2; 53 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of files on pertaining to various projects undertaken by the Society. These include the Delinquency Prevention Programme, What Breaking the Law Could Mean to You, conducted in high schools; the Seventh Step, a program of alcohol recovery based on Alcoholics Anonymous established specifically for inmates of correctional facilities, Alternative Measures, Family House, Hobden House, Prison sentence programs, Impaired drivers program, and the Citizen Participation Programme, aimed at getting the public interested and involved in correctional issues. The subseries also consists of proposals for other programs that may not have received funding.
    - Projects Proposed 1973-74, 1973 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Family Service Apr. 1979 - Mar. 1980 Vol. 4, 1979 - 1980; F-1-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Seattle Project, 1972-76, 1972 - 1976; F-1-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Family Service Development Project, 1976 - 1979; F-1-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - 7 Steps Donne, 1970 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Prospecting Course, 1979; F-1-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Youth Containment, 1977 - 1980; F-1-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Delinquency Prevention Programme Vol. 1, 1977-78 Requests, 1977 - 1978; F-1-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 1-27)
    - Delinquency Prevention Programme 1978-79 Requests, 1978 - 1979; F-1-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Citizen Participation Programme, 1973 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Matsqui Volunteers, 1973 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Community Service, 1976 - 1979; F-1-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Alternative Measures, 1986 - 1990; F-1-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Community projects funding, 1986 - 1990; F-1-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - financial, 1982 - 1984; F-1-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - couples program, 1988 - 1991; F-1-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - building, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - mortgage, 1988 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - reports and recommendations, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - historical documents, 1983 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - mortgage appeals, 1988 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - correspondence, 1988 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - proposal for expansion of Abbotsford family house, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Family house - zoning, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Forensic psychiatric, 1987 - 1988; F-1-3-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hands across the border, 1989; F-1-3-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - budget, 1983 - 1984; F-1-3-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - contract, 1989; F-1-3-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - historical documents, 1983 - 1995; F-1-3-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - lease / mortgage, 1984 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - special investigations, 1986 - 1988; F-1-3-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 1-89)
    - Hobden house - zoning, 1984 - 1987; F-1-3-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Prison sentence program, 1985 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Prison sentence program proposal, 1987; F-1-3-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Prison sentence program correspondence, 1986 - 1988; F-1-3-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Prison sentence program - statistics, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Proposals - introduction (generic form), 1988; F-1-3-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Proposals - adjunct housing, 1987; F-1-3-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - RFPs community service program, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - RFPs drugs and alcohol program, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Proposal - impaired drivers, 1988; F-1-3-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Proposal - substance abuse, alcohol, Fraser region, 1989; F-1-3-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Proposal - urban native women, 1989; F-1-3-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Choices film proposal, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - appraisal, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - building, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - couples program, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - historical documents, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - mortgage, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - mortgage appeals, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house women - together, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Family house - zoning, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Forensic psychiatric correspondence & contract, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Hands across the border, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Hobden house - historical documents, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Hobden house - zoning, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Operation Wok, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Parole contract & correspondence, 1990 - 1991; F-1-3-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Prison visiting - volunteer manual, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - History - John Trombley, 1990 - 1994; F-1-3-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Forensic residential house, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Impaired drivers program, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Impaired drivers program, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Impaired drivers program, 1990; F-1-3-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Siblings, 1973 - 1975; F-1-3-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - Bail and divorce (minus-one), 1973 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - Federal local initiatives program, 1971 - 1973; F-1-3-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - Dial X, 1973; F-1-3-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - Family service, 1972 - 1974; F-1-3-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - Family service, 1975 - 1978; F-1-3-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 1-93)
    - LINC society of BC, 1974 - 1975; F-1-3-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Criminal justice diversion project, 1974 - 1975; F-1-3-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
    - Unemployment insurance commission annual report, 1974; F-1-3-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 1-94)
  - Supporting organizations, 1961 - 1994; F-1-3-3; 76 cm of textual records 9 photographs
    Subseries consists of files relating to the work of the Society with various organizations closely involved in parole supervision, corrections and penitentiaries, especially at the federal level. There are also correspondence files for each prison in British Columbia, the Libby society, the Elizabeth Fry society, and the Coalition against the return of the death penalty.
    - Provincial Corrections - General, 1969-1974 Vol. 1, F-1-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Provincial Corrections - General, 1975-1980 Vol. 2, F-1-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Provincial Corrections - Justice Development Commission 1974-76, 1974 - 1976; F-1-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Forensic Services Commission, 1973 - 1975; F-1-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Corrections - Federal, 1961 - 1971; F-1-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 1-28)
    - Federal Correction - General 1973 Vol. 2, F-1-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Correction - General 1974 Vol. 3, F-1-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Correction - General 1980 Vol. 4, F-1-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Parole - Aug. 1968 - July 1972 Vol. 1, 1968 - 1972; F-1-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Parole - Aug. 1972 - Mar. 1976 Vol. 2, 1972 - 1976; F-1-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Parole - Aug. 1976 - Dec. 1977 Vol. 3, 1976 - 1977; F-1-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 1-29)
    - Federal Parole - General Jun. 1978 - Mar. 31, 1981 Vol. 4, 1978 - 1981; F-1-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Federal Penitentiary - General 1973-1979 Vol. 1, F-1-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Private Agencies Task Force, 1974 - 1978; F-1-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Special Employment Field Services, 1973; F-1-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Canada Community Services Projects, 1980; F-1-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Company Of Young Canadians, 1970 - 1972; F-1-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Alternatives in Action, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - BC agencies consulting on criminal justice, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Coalition against return of death penalty, 1986 - 1987; F-1-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Elizabeth Fry society, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Libby society, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Literacy BC, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Agendas, minutes, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Other provinces - Newfoundland, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Provincial groups, [ca 1990] - 1990; F-1-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - USA - Washington, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Programs & facilities, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Ford mountain, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Photographs of prisons, [ca 1950] - 1990; F-1-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Kent institution, 1990 - 1992; F-1-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Mission institution, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Mountain institution, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Regional psychiatric centre, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Vancouver pre-trial, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - William Head, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Womens institutions, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - BC agencies consulting on criminal justice, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Elizabeth Fry society, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Legal services society, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Literacy BC, 1990; F-1-3-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 1-92)
    - Resources - conditional release supervision, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Resources - community care facility act, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Prison visiting guide, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Programs - contracts and correspondence, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Alouette Lake, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Elbow Lake, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Ferndale, 1987 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Kent *correspondence from Stephen Reid*, 1983 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Matsqui, 1985 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Mission, 1985 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Mountain, 1983 - 1985; F-1-3-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 1-97)
    - Mountain, 1987; F-1-3-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Mountain, 1988; F-1-3-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Mountain, 1989; F-1-3-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Twin Maples, 1983; F-1-3-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Prison services contracts, 1985 - 1988; F-1-3-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Parole - Vancouver - contracts, 1983 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - Hobden house - contract, 1985 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 1-98)
    - US Visitation - contracts & correspondence, 1988 - 1991; F-1-3-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - Family house - contracts, 1984 - 1989; F-1-3-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - Hobden house - contract, 1991 - 1994; F-1-3-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - New Page, 1991 - 1992; F-1-3-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 1-99)
    - Hobden house - contract, 1992 - 1994; F-1-3-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Parole - general, 1987 - 1990; F-1-3-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - General, 1988 - 1994; F-1-3-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 1-100)
    - Parole - Abbotsford, 1988 - 1990; F-1-3-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Parole - Abbotsford, 1988 - 1992; F-1-3-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Parole - Vancouver, 1988 - 1994; F-1-3-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Parole - Vancouver, 1993 - 1994; F-1-3-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Parole - Vancouver, 1991 - 1993; F-1-3-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
    - Prison services contracts, 1988 - 1992; F-1-3-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 1-101)
  - Resource clients, 1967 - 1990; F-1-3-4; 38 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of files on various topics, including alcoholism, community residential centres, psychiatry, electronic monitoring program, recividism, sentencing, death penalty, and multiculturalism. The files contain reports, papers, pamphlets, newspaper clippings and some correspondence on these miscellaneous topics.
    - Bonding, 1967 - 1976; F-1-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Legal, 1970 - 1980; F-1-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Alcoholism - General, 1968 - 1973; F-1-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 1-30)
    - Psychiatry, 1969 - 1974; F-1-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - Indian Court Worker - General, 1969 - 1975; F-1-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - Indian Court Worker - John Howard Society, 1969 - 1976; F-1-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - Job Finders, 1973 - 1975; F-1-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - Gestalt Therapy Training and Demonstration Project Fund, 1969 - 1971; F-1-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - Community Residential Centres, 1974 - 1976; F-1-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - 7th Step Programme, 1970 - 1972; F-1-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 1-31)
    - 7th Step, 1973 - 1975; F-1-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - Hunter Creek Lodge, 1974 - 1981; F-1-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - X-Kalay, 1970 - 1972; F-1-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - X-Kalay Foundation, 1973 - 1980; F-1-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - Davidson's Acres, 1971 - 1975; F-1-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - Native Indian Half-Way House Projects, 1969 - 1972; F-1-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 1-32)
    - Electronic monitoring program, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Death penalty, 1987; F-1-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 1-90)
    - Electronic monitoring program advisory committee, 1987 - 1990; F-1-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Family violence resource program, 1989; F-1-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Multiculturalism - forum, 1989; F-1-3-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Privatization material, 1984 - 1986; F-1-3-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Privatization correspondence, 1984 - 1986; F-1-3-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Security checks - documents, 1980 - 1989; F-1-3-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Sentencing - public perception, 1986; F-1-3-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 1-91)
    - Electronic monitoring program, 1990; F-1-3-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 1-92)